No te dejaré hacer esto.
Veronica, listen to me.
The company needs this money
to cover financial gaps.
Go to hell, Mason.
You mean nothing to this family.
And you're even not my real husband.
And you will never be.
Never!
I don't care.
You can live your life
however you want.
This is just business.
More!
Okay, give it to me.
I think you've had enough for tonight.
Maybe it's time to slow down.
Anthony.
Your job
was to come here,
not to lecture me.
Their “happy marriage”
didn't even last year.
While Mason Powell is working
like a dog,
it seems Aspen is losing
the run of herself.
Oh, and here we go.
Mason Powell himself.
Grab your popcorn.
It's about to get interesting.